Register of the Rodolfo Echeverría Martínez Collection, 1911-1986
Hoover Institution Archives
- OVERSIZE FILE, 1911-1981
  - Newsletters, circulars, and newspapers, relating to the Mexican revolution, the PCM Central Committee, agrarian issues, Mexican politics, international affairs, and trade unions. Some of this material corresponds to the SUBJECT FILE series; the original oversize copies of other materials (which have been photocopied and placed in the collection), are also included. (Box 36)
- PHONOTAPES
  - One reel labelled "Campa, 20 mujeres y 1 hombre," 1976 June 18 (Tape-cabinet Tape cabinet)